depedclub.com 2018-07-27

# Privacy Policy - The Deped Teachers Club

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving our Website.

By using our Website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

#### **  
Information Collection And Use**

While using our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personal information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personal information may include, but is not limited to your Name, Email Address, Your Website URL or your social media account details.

#### **  
Log Data**

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this.

#### **  
Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you via email with newsletters, website updates, member responses, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of relevant to you.

#### **  
Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### **  
Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 2, 2016 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically.

Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

#### **  
Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please Contact us.
